ILGWU David Dubinsky Correspondence 5780/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Manacher, Irving A., 1967-1970 (Box 438, Folder 10)
- Membership Lists, 1958-1964 (Box 439, Folder 1)
  Statistical data.
- Messages of Condolence, 1962-1978 (Box 439, Folder 2-3)
- Messages of Congratulation, 1966-1974 (Box 439, Folder 4)
- N, 1968-1977 (Box 439, Folder 5)
- Nat'l. Board of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1965-1969 (Box 439, Folder 6)
- New Leader, 1967-1973 (Box 439, Folder 7)
- New York City Matters, 1967-1971 (Box 439, Folder 8)
  I.c.w. John V. Lindsay.
- New York State Matters, 1966-1968 (Box 439, Folder 9)
  I.c.w. Nelson A. Rockefeller.
- New York State Electoral College, 1968-1972 (Box 439, Folder 10)
  D.D. as elector.
- New York Times, 1967-1976 (Box 439, Folder 11)
- Newspapers, 1967-1975 (Box 439, Folder 12)
- Nixon, Richard M., 1960-1970 (Box 439, Folder 13)
  Incl. four Nixon letters.
- Novik, Morris S., 1943-1971 (Box 439, Folder 14)
- O, 1975-1980 (Box 439, Folder 15)
- Office and Professional Employees' Int'l. Union, Local 153, 1965-1971 (Box 439, Folder 16)
- Officers, Vice Presidents, ILGWU, 1966 (Box 439, Folder 17)
- P, 1966-1977 (Box 440, Folder 1)
- Pegler, Westbrook, 1940-1963 (Box 440, Folder 2)
- Pins and Needles, 1966-1974 (Box 440, Folder 3)
- Political Dept., 1966-1971 (Box 440, Folder 4)
  Incl. legislative newsletters.
- Politics, 1971-1976 (Box 440, Folder 5)
- Politics, 1970 (Box 440, Folder 6-7)
- Politics, NYC, 1969 (Box 440, Folder 8-9)
  Incl. voting records of congressmen.
- Politics, 1968 (Box 440, Folder 10)
- Politics, 1966-1967 (Box 441, Folder 1)
- Politics, 1966 (Box 441, Folder 2)
- Politics. Liberal Party, 1976-1980 (Box 441, Folder 3)
- Politics. Liberal Party, 1971-1975 (Box 441, Folder 4)
- Politics. Liberal Party, 1968-1970 (Box 441, Folder 5-6)
- Politics. Liberal Party, 1967 (Box 441, Folder 7)
- Politics. Liberal Party, 1965-1966 (Box 441, Folder 8)
- Politics. Liberal Party, 1946-1972 (Box 442, Folder 1)
  Contributions.
- Politics. Liberal Party, 1966-1972 (Box 442, Folder 2)
- Portnoy, Samuel A., 1973-1979 (Box 442, Folder 3)
  Corres. re his book on Vladimir Medem.
- President's Advisory Committee on Labor Management Policy, U.S. Department of Commerce, 1961-1969 (Box 442, Folder 4-8)
- Puerto Rico, 1966-1976 (Box 442, Folder 9)
- R, 1966-1977 (Box 443, Folder 1-4)
- Requests, 1972 (Box 443, Folder 3)
- Requests, 1970-1971 (Box 443, Folder 4-5)
- Requests, 1969 (Box 443, Folder 6-7)
- Requests, 1968 (Box 443, Folder 8-9)
- Requests, 1965-1967 (Box 444, Folder 1)
- Requests, 1966-1967 (Box 444, Folder 2)
  Discussed with Louis Stulberg.
- Requests. A, 1962-1974 (Box 444, Folder 3)
- Requests. A, 1956-1971 (Box 444, Folder 4)
  Incl. Arthritis Foundation.
- Requests. B-C, 1968-1979 (Box 444, Folder 5)
  Incl. Congress for Jewish Culture.
- Requests. D-G, 1968-1977 (Box 444, Folder 6)
  Incl. Eugene V. Debs Foundation.
- Requests. H, 1962-1972 (Box 444, Folder 7)
  Incl. Henry Street Settlement, Hospital for Special Surgery of the Margaret M. Caspary Clinic.
- Requests. I-L, 1945-1975 (Box 444, Folder 8)
  Incl. LaGuardia Memorial Association; Liberal Party Campaign Committee.
- Requests. M-P, 1939-1976 (Box 444, Folder 9)
- Requests. R., 1966-1976 (Box 444, Folder 10)
  Incl. A. Philip Randolph Institute and A. Reisen Fund.
- Requests. S-U, 1957-1976 (Box 445, Folder 1)
- Requests. W-Z, 1968-1976 (Box 445, Folder 2)
  Incl. Die Zukunft.
- Requests, 1939-1974 (Box 445, Folder 3)
  Workmen's Circle.
- Research Dept., 1960-1977 (Box 445, Folder 4-5)
- Retirement Fund Dept., 1970-1972 (Box 445, Folder 6)
- Retirement Inquiries, 1969-1972 (Box 445, Folder 7)
- Retirement Inquiries, 1968 (Box 445, Folder 8-9)
- Retirement Inquiries, 1967 (Box 446, Folder 1-2)
- Retirement Inquiries, 1966 (Box 446, Folder 3)
- Retirement Inquiries, 1965 (Box 446, Folder 4-5)
- Retirement, Officers, 1965-1970 (Box 446, Folder 6)
- Riesel, Victor, 1967-1971 (Box 446, Folder 7)
- Romualdi, Serafino, 1967 (Box 446, Folder 8)
  Incl. manuscript of U.S. activity in Latin America.
- Roosevelt Institute, Eleanor, 1972-1981 (Box 446, Folder 9-10)
  Nov. 1972-81. Incl. Eleanor Roosevelt Memorial Foundation, 1971-Nov. 1972.
- Roosevelt Institute, Eleanor, 1967-1970 (Box 447, Folder 1-2)
- Roosevelt Institute, Eleanor, 1964-1966 (Box 447, Folder 3-5)
- Roosevelt Institute, Eleanor, 1962-1963 (Box 447, Folder 6-8)
- Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1940-1977 (Box 447, Folder 9)
  Incl. three FDR letters.
- Roosevelt-University, 1966-1971 (Box 447, Folder 10)
- S, 1966-1978 (Box 448, Folder 1-2)
- Schlesinger, Abraham, 1947-1966 (Box 448, Folder 3)
- Schlesinger, Schlesinger, Schlesinger, 1962-1974 (Box 448, Folder 4)
- Speeches and Statements, 1965-1975 (Box 448, Folder 5-6)
- Staff Matters, 1956-1971 (Box 448, Folder 7)
- Stulberg, Louis, 1966-1978 (Box 448, Folder 8)
- Supplementary Unemployment Benefits Fund, ILGWU, 1967-1968 (Box 448, Folder 9)
- T, 1968-1977 (Box 448, Folder 10)
- Temple University, 1964-1967 (Box 448, Folder 11)
  Awarded degree of Doctor of Humane Letters, 1964.
- Time Magazine Dinner, 1963 (Box 448, Folder 12)
- Truman Library Institute, Harry S., 1969-1980 (Box 448, Folder 13)
- Tyler, Gus, 1966-1972 (Box 449, Folder 1-2)
- U, 1967-1977 (Box 449, Folder 3)
- Union Health Center, 1950-1977 (Box 449, Folder 4-5)
- Unions, 1967-1979 (Box 449, Folder 6-7)
- Unions, United Automobile Workers, 1966-1974 (Box 449, Folder 8-9)
  I.c.w. Walter Reuther.
- U.S. Government Departments, 1967-1981 (Box 449, Folder 10)
- U.S. Dept. of Labor, 1966-1969 (Box 449, Folder 11)
- Unity House, 1966-1973 (Box 449, Folder 12)
- V, 1971-1979 (Box 449, Folder 13)
- W, 1967-1977 (Box 450, Folder 1)
- Weiss, Shmuel, 1968-1977 (Box 450, Folder 2)
- Wolf and Schulman, 1956-1979 (Box 450, Folder 3)
- (New York) World-Telegram and The Sun, 1943-1959 (Box 450, Folder 4)
  I.c.w. Roy W. Howard of Scripps-Howard newspapers and Fred Woltman.
- X-Y-Z, 1973-1975 (Box 450, Folder 5)
- Newspaper Clippings. (Box 450, Folder 6-7)
- Newspaper Clippings. (Box 451)
- Appointment Books, 1942-1945 (Box 452, Folder 1)
- Appointment Books, 1946-1949 (Box 452, Folder 2)
- Appointment Books, 1950-1954 (Box 452, Folder 3)
- Appointment Books, 1954-1955 (Box 452, Folder 4)
- Appointment Books, 1956-1957 (Box 452, Folder 5)
- Appointment Books, 1957-1958 (Box 452, Folder 6)
- Appointment Books, 1959-1961 (Box 452, Folder 7)
- Appointment Books, 1962-1966 (Box 452, Folder 8)
- Appointment Books, 1967-1970 (Box 452, Folder 9)
- Appointment Books and Calendars, 1971-1972 (Box 452, Folder 10)
- Appointment Books and Calendars, 1973-1974 (Box 452, Folder 11)
- Calendars, 1942 (Box 452, Folder 12)
- Calendars, 1943 (Box 452, Folder 13)
- Daily Diaries, 1944-1945 (Box 453, Folder 1)
- Daily Diaries, 1946-1948 (Box 453, Folder 2)
- Daily Diaries, 1950-1951 (Box 453, Folder 3)
- Daily Diaries, 1951-1952 (Box 453, Folder 4)
- Daily Diaries, 1953-1959 (Box 453, Folder 5)
- Daily Diaries, 1960-1961 (Box 453, Folder 6)
- Daily Diaries, 1964-1965 (Box 453, Folder 7)
- Daily Diaries, 1966-1967 (Box 453, Folder 8)
- Daily Diaries, 1968-1969 (Box 453, Folder 9)
- Daily Diaries, 1970-1971 (Box 453, Folder 10)
- Health, Housing and Social Services, 1967 (Box 453, Folder 11)
- Labor, Civil Service and Public Pensions, 1967 (Box 453, Folder 12)
- Memoir (Box 457)
  David Dubinsky: A Life With Labor by David Dubinsky and A.H. Raskin.
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Materials. Newspaper Clippings and Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 457, Folder 1)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Materials (Box 457, Folder 2)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Materials (Box 457, Folder 3)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Materials (Box 457, Folder 4)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Materials. Transcribed Notes (Box 457, Folder 5)
- "David Dubinsky: Herald of Labor Change" (Box 457, Folder 6)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Materials. Drafts, 1973 (Box 457, Folder 7)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Materials (Box 457, Folder 8)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Materials (Box 457, Folder 9)
- Memoir (Box 458)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Recordings 1-6 (Box 458, Folder 1)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Recordings 1-6 (2) (Box 458, Folder 2)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Recordings 7-12 (Box 458, Folder 3)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Recordings 7-12 (2) (Box 458, Folder 4)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Recordings 13-20 (Box 458, Folder 5)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Recordings 21-26 (Box 458, Folder 6)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Recordings 28-38 (Box 458, Folder 7)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Recordings Miscellaneous 18-49 (Box 458, Folder 8)
- Dubinsky David. Memoir Recordings 39-47 (Box 458, Folder 9)
- Dubinsky, David. Memoir Materials from AJ Goldberg, Louis Stulberg and George Meany (Box 458, Folder 10)
- Dubinsky, David. Miscellaneous Memoir Materials (Box 458, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Memorabilia. (Box 461)
  Incl. scrapbooks of pictures and awards.
- Poster - Do your share for a free Italy. (Box 462)
- Text digitized from the collection. (Box 463)